I got a sports facility we're generating about three and a half million a year, but my question is not about this
Okay, my question is about my wife we have to talk
14 years ago. I opened the first the only professional team here in Vegas
And I failed miserably and the fourth year my wife told me it's either the the team knew we're divorcing now
I know how why I failed and
Here I am with an opportunity to bring the team back
Okay, should I go and do it the right way this time or this is something that if you feel
You know why you have a good thing going on. Why go back to something bad from a business perspective
It's actually I think it's fairly black and white so you don't have a business question
You have a life question the framework that I would use I like the regret minimization framework
I'm looking at 85 year old me coming back to the present and saying like would I be okay with
Failing at this business and torpedoing the one that was working so that I could say I had a shot because you can't play out
Oh, I get you know the team becomes a billion dollar company. Well. It's like yeah, of course. We'll do that one right
But we have to look at what's the worst-case scenario and am I okay with that worst-case scenario if I'm okay with the worst-case scenario
Then I would take the swing if I'm not okay
Then I just say that I'm not going to sleep with every woman, and I will have to get married at some point